<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>(no title)</title><link>https://hartmantam.xyz/</link><description>Recent content on (no title)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a [Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hartmantam.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://hartmantam.xyz/privacy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 15:37:02 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://hartmantam.xyz/privacy/</guid><description>1. Introduction Welcome to (no title) (&amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;our,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;). We are committed to respecting the privacy and data protection rights of our users. This Privacy Policy outlines how we collect, use, and safeguard your personal information when you visit our website. Please take a moment to read this Privacy Policy carefully.
2. Information We Collect We use Umami, an open source and privacy-focused analytics platform, to gather aggregated and anonymized information about your interactions with our website.</description></item><item><title>Samba over Tailscale/Wireguard</title><link>https://hartmantam.xyz/tech/samba-over-tailscale-wireguard/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hartmantam.xyz/tech/samba-over-tailscale-wireguard/</guid><description>Edit: I rewritten my old article as that was too long and too many irrelevant things. As my instructor said, technical documentation need to get straight on point, any other else are considered lard. But, if you like lard, I still have the old version up.
I will show how to serve Samba share over Tailscale in a secure and (some what) hidden manner. I don&amp;rsquo;t imply that SMB over Internet is not secure, but I&amp;rsquo;m more confident with Tailscale, or actually Wireguard that running under the hood.</description></item><item><title>Samba over Tailscale/Wireguard [Old]</title><link>https://hartmantam.xyz/hidden/samba-over-tailscale-wireguard-old/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 18:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hartmantam.xyz/hidden/samba-over-tailscale-wireguard-old/</guid><description>I recently found out about Tailscale, a control plane for WireGuard. I decided to revisit an old project of mine and use it to set up a Samba server on an long ignored dedicated server so that I could access my videos remotely. However, the process proved to be more challenging than I had anticipated.
Goal The goal was to access my videos from the server via my Windows PC and Android phone, while also ensuring that the data was secure in transit, and not accessed by others.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://hartmantam.xyz/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://hartmantam.xyz/about/</guid><description>Comming Soon</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://hartmantam.xyz/tech/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://hartmantam.xyz/tech/hello-world/</guid><description>I don&amp;rsquo;t know why, but I want to have a blog long ago. I always have a vague idea of documenting little things that I learnt but never took action, or failed to complete the post and give up mid-way.
TBH, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what will be posted here but by starting with this post I believe it is a good direction I&amp;rsquo;m heading.
Still, I don&amp;rsquo;t know when and what I will post.</description></item></channel></rss>